Finding Aid for Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers
Clarke Historical Library
- Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers.
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,December 7, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ruth Ludlow,December 9, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,December 12, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mamie Marble,December 12, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Doris,December 14, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,December 15, 28, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna,December 15, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edith,December 16, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie,December 16, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jeanne,December 17, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mauice,December 18, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: unidentified,December 18, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Carolyn, and Alice,December 20, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edward, Theresa, and Betty,December 22, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Parker,December 28, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,January 2, 22, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,January 5, 19, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. Pruda Wise,January 6, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Jean Ahbatha,January 8, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edith and Charles,January 12, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ruth,January 14, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Parker,January 15, 24, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Shirley, Alan, and Dana, Jr. Parker,January 17, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,February 6, 26, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence to: NDF 1: Thelma Hayes,February 17, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 124)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: MaryBelle,February 19, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 125)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,February 22, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 126)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Charlene, Clyde, and Charles Greenman,February 23, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 127)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,February 27, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 128)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,March 13, 16, 24, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 129)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Geraldine,March 3, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 130)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ruth Clawson,March 5, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 131)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Wilson H. Davis From: Gerty Davis,March 15, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,March 16, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Matie, Jud, and Lura,March 17, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 134)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertrude Harrington,March 20, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,March 28, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 136)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edith and Charles,April 1, 18, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,April 9, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jud, Matie, and Lura,April 14, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,April 23, 27, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ruth Stringer,April 25, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,April 25, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 142)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,May 1, 7, 18, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 143)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jud, Matie, and Lura,May 2, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jo,May 7, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 145)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,May 13, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 146)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,May 27, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 147)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Almeda Burgess,June 8, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,June 22, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 149)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,July 1, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 150)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,July 6, 23, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Doris,July 9, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,July 14, 21, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Miss C. Keltz,July 15, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 154)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Eva Robertson,July 20, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 155)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: The Ruffs,July 22, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 156)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry (Geraldine) Finley,August 6, 29, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,August 17, 19, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 158)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Eva Robertson,September 6, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 159)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,September 7, 10, 30, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 160)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Matie,September 11, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley and Kent,September 14, 25, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Genevieve,September 17, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Matie,September 18, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 164)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ruth Stringer,September 26, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 165)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Pruda Wise,September 28, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 166)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,October 16, 31, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 167)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Kilburn,October 21, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 168)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,October 26, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 169)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,October 30, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 170)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy E. Ruff,October 30, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 171)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,November 2-3, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 172)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,November 7, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 173)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Eva Robertson,November 10, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 174)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,November 19, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 175)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,November 28, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 176)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ruth Stringer,December 3, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 177)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Burt and Bertie,December 10, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 178)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,December 12, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 179)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Pruda Wise,December 13, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 180)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Matie, Jud, and Lura,December 14, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 181)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ruth Ludlow,December 18, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 182)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,December 18, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 183)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. L. D. Abbott,December 23, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 184)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Charlotte,December 24, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 185)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. Dana Parker,December 24, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 186)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bessie,December 27, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 187)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,December 28, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 188)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Almeda Burgess,December 29, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 189)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,January 2, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 190)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,January 3, 25, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 191)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,January 5, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 192)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dee Coater,January 9, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 193)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley and Kent,January 10, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 194)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jud, Matie, and Lura,January 11, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,January 15, 20, 29, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Parker,January 20, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zarita Saxton,January 29, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Pruda Wise,February 4, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,February 4, 12, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,February 10, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,February 15, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edith Sheehan,February 26, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,March 2, 7, 9, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,March 2, 17, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,March 13, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Parker,March 17, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina Grindatti,March 20, 31, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,March 20, 31, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 209)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,April 1-2, 15, 28, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 210)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley,April 3, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 211)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,April 4, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 212)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Charlotte,April 11, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 213)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina Grindatti,April 14, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 214)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,April 20, 23, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 215)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,May 5, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 216)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ruth Stringer,May 6, 21, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 217)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,June 11, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 218)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,June 28, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 219)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,July 7, 11, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 220)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,July 15, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 221)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,August 7, 23, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,September 6, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 223)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Kent (of Theron and Jerry Finley),September 13, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 224)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,September 27, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 225)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,October 11, 18, 28, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 226)
  - Correspondence to: NDF (Mom, Grandmother) From: Dorothy Finley,November 1, 3, 8, 28, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 227)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Libbie Elmer,November 3, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 228)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ethel,November 5, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 229)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley,November 29, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 230)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley,December 4, 21, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 231)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,December 8, 26, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 232)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley and Kent,January 4, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,January 22, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,February 1, 13, 20, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,February 23, 28, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley,February 17, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,March 10, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,March 12, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Kent,March 29, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,April 9, 22, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley,April 10-11, 24, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley,April 26, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W, Finley,May [no day], 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley and Kent,May 2, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Dorothy, and Pamela Finley,May 4, 6, 10, 23, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,June 19, 26, 30, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley and Kent,June 6, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,July 3, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,July 17, 24, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley and Kent,July 12, 30, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,August 5, 15, 23, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,August 24, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley and Kent,August 31, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,September 17, 27, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley and Kent,September 6, 27, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,October 13, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,October 24, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,November 4, 30, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 11, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley and Kent,November 13, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,December 5, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,December 28, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley and Kent,January 11, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,January 25, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 6, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,February 21, 24, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley and Kent,March 6, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,March 20, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,April 10, 20?, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,April 28, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,May 7, 15-16, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,June 14, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,July 2, 10, 20, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,July 31, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,August 7, 12, 23, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,August 27, 31, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,August 15, 26, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley and Kent,September 10, 21, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,September 16, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,September 17, 24, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,October 2, 7, 15, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,October 20-21, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence to: Jerry Finley From: Theron W. Finley,October 15, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley,October 15, 25, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,November 2, 6, 13, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,November 18, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina and John Grindatti,November 8, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,November 20, 23, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,November 26, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,December 1, 26, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Western Union (Notice of Theron's Injury),December 12, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Western Union (Notice of Theron's Injury),January 15, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Newell,December 26, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Dorothy Finley,January 6, 20, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence to: Jerry Finley and Kent From: Theron W. Finley,January 8, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley and Kent,January 9, 11, 18, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,February 4, 19, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry C. Finley,February 12, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley,February 15, 18, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Navy Department,February 21, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,March 22, 26, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,March 23, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,March 25, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: John Grindatti,March 29, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,April 9, 30, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley,April 10, 14, 26, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,May 7, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina Grindatti,May 12, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,May 14, 31, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,June 17, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,June 18, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley,July 2, 11, 17, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,July 12, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,August 10, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley,August 27, 29, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina Grindatti,September 5, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron and Jerry Finley,September 4, 20, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,September 27, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,October 12, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,November 5, 27, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,November 15, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nina Grindatti,November 20, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,December 14, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,December 28, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Marydena Davis,January 3, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,January 7, 26, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,January 3, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,February 13, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,February 13, 27, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley,February 27, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Theron W. Finley,March 16, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,April 1, 23, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,April 17, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,April 29, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,May 4, 8, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,May 6, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy and Harry Finley,June 1, 5, 26, 30, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,July 15, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,August 11, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Dorothy Finley,September 2, 7, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,September 3, 26, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,October 2, 27, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Marydena Davis,October 9, 1952, undated (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,October 30, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,November 8, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Wilson and Gerty Davis,November 9, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley,November 14, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,December 9, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,December 12 1952 (Box 18, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Adrian, Loraine, and Garth DeKorte,December 10, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,January 9-10, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,January 13, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edward Finley,January 14, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence to: NDF, Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Dorothy Finley, Gerty Davis,January 17, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Wilson L. Davis,January 25, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 124)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Wilson L. Davis,February 1, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 125)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,April 30, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 126)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry Finley,May 5, 14, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 127)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Emmy Honeywell,May 20, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 128)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Marydena and Gene Duckworth,June 27, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 129)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley,July 4, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 130)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gerty Davis,July 9, [no day], 1953 (Box 18, Folder 131)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Finley,August 2, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 132)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. Albam Mehling,August 12, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 133)